List of commands and any relevant quotes

.help
  Basically it's a short introduction to Tumble and a list of commands. Call it yourself and Tumble whispers it to you.

.roll
  "From 1-6, you got a... [ 6 ]"
.roll pizza
  "I-I don't have any dice like that..."
.d20
  "From 1-20, you got a... [ 1 ]"
  "Somewhere, an anvil falls on an Umbreon..." (Hidden d20 quote for natural 1's. :3)


.mushroom
  "With two dice, you rolled 5 and 5! The total is... [ 10 ]"
  "Hey, you got doubles!" (if... you get doubles, obviously)

.coinflip
  "The coin came up... [ Heads ]"

.chance 
  (Tumble says nothing for this)

.capsule 
  "You opened the capsule, and found... [ Mushroom ]"

.torracat
  "Torracat decrees that the following shall happen! [ Torracat Revolution ]"

.mining
  "After some digging, you found... [ Protector ]"

.bonus1
  "The first award is... [ I dunno ]"

.bonus2
  "The second award is... [ Some kinda award ]"

.bonus3
  "The third award is... [ Samba would know ]"

.torrashuffle Player1 Player2 Player3 Umbreon
  "Player1 moves to Player2's position!
  Player2 moves to Player1's original position!
  Player3 doesn't move!
  Umbreon doesn't move!" (If .torrashuffle is called without player names, they're called Player 1, Player 2, etc. )

.itemshuffle Player1 Player2 Player3 Umbreon
  "Player1, you can keep your item.
  Player2, give your item to Player3!
  Player3, give your item to Umbreon!
  Umbreon, give your item to Player2!" (Same as with .torrashuffle regarding player names.)

.torracatrevolution 40 60 55 45
  "Everyone now has 50 coins!"
.torracatrevolution
  "Please specify everyone's total number of coins!
  Usage example: .torracatrevolution 10 20 15 20"
.torracatrevolution 50 45 ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
  "ABSOLUTELY isn't a valid number of coins!
  Usage example: .torracatrevolution 10 20 15 20"

.thwomp
  "Blue Thwomp: 2
  Green Thwomp: 1
  Violet Thwomp: 3"

.sslblock
  "You bashed the block, and out fell... [ 24 coins! ]"

.machoketoss
  "The Machoke balled you up and threw you to the upper right corner's ? Space!
  (If you're already there, go to the lower left space instead.)

.sportsball
  "An Electrode rolls up to you and explodes! You lose 20 coins!"
.sportsball
  "A Golem Ball comes and rolls over you! You'll stay flattened, unable to move for a turn."

.boocoins
  "Boo stole 15 coins!"

.randomitem
  "Your item is... [ Hammer ]" (This is used in Malie Garden specifically.)

.maliewater
  "A Feebas flies out of the water and splashes around! Nothing happens."
.maliewater
  "Corsola excitedly flies out of the water and lands on you!
  You've been half-flattened! Your next turn's roll will be a half roll, and you can't use items."
.maliewater
  "Octillery pops out of the water. Unhappy to see you, they blast you with an Octazooka.
  You're blasted back to Start! You won't get any of the benefits from reaching Start."
.maliewater
  "Milotic pops out of the water. Glad to have a visitor, they give you a small gift.
  You got 10 coins!"
.maliewater
  "Manaphy flies out of the water, looking overjoyed! In their good mood, they're happy to give you a very nice gift!
  You got a Star!"

.meowth
  "The coin has been flipped. It comes up...
  Heads! Did you win?"

.maliestar
  "The Star is now in location 5!" (Comes with an image... maybe the number is kinda meaningless.)


---------------------------
These commands are just fun, silly ones. They're not a high priority, and can be removed.
---------------------------
.wakeup
  "zzz... ...oh... Oh! Ah! I-I'm awake! I'm ready for a party! Always!"
.thanks
  (Samba could say any number of things for this, from 0 to 1000.)
  "Aw, it's my pleasure! <3"
  "No problem, buddy! <3"
  "Always happy to help! <3"
  "You're very welcome! <3"
  "Not a problem! <3"
  "Don't mention it! <3"
  "Any time, friend! <3"
  "Let me know if you need more help! <3"
  "Hey, it's what I'm here for! <3"
  "Heehee~ <3"
.hi
  (Samba could say any number of things for this, from 0 to 1000.)
  "Hello there!"
  "Hi! Ready for a party?"
  "Hello hello~"
  "Hiiiii!"
  "Howdy!"
  "Hey hey!"
  "Hi, buddy!"
  "Hi! Good seeing you again!"
.rigged
  "I am not! :triumph:"
.ping
  "Pong! ♪"